// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The police have arrested the criminals. / The criminals ..................... by the police.",
    answer: "have been arrested",
    options: [ "are arrested", "have been arresting","have been arrested","have being arrested" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "They congratulated the winners. / The winners ........................by them.",
    answer: "were congratulated",
    options: ["are congratulated","were congratulated","were being congratulated","was being congratulated "]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"The teacher admonished the child. / The child ................................. by the teacher.",
    answer: "was admonished",
    options: [
      "has admonished", "is admonished","was admonished","will being admonished" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "She makes dolls. / Dolls ............................... by her.",
    answer: "are made",
    options: ["made","are making","are made","will made" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Birds make nests. / Nests ............................ by birds.",
    answer: "are made",
    options: [ "are made", "are making","were made","will being making" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "I have completed the project. / The project ................................ by me.",
    answer: "has been completed",
    options: ["was completed", "have been completed","have been completed","has been completed"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "She prepared the report. / The report ............................... by her.",
    answer: "was prepared",
    options: [ "was prepared", "is prepared","were prepared","has prepared" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "He has launched a business. / A business ................................ by him.",
    answer: "has been launched",
    options: [ "is launched", "has been launched","was launched","were launched" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: " I have sent the invites. / The invites ............................... by me.",
    answer: "have been sent",
    options: [ "are sent", "were sent","will being sent","have been sent" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "I am feeding the dogs. / The dogs …………………………… by me.",
    answer: "are being fed",
    options: [  "are fed", "were being fed","are being fed","was fed"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: " Doctors treat patients. / Patients …………………………. by doctors.",
    answer: "are treated",
    options: [  "treated", "have treated","are being treated","are treated" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "He was serving drinks. / Drinks ................................ by him.",
    answer: "were being served",
    options: [  "were served", "are being served","were being served","was being served" ]
  },
];